What is done cannot be undone.
The Djinn is a horror, thriller film directed by David Charbonier.
A mute boy is trapped in his apartment with a sinister monster when he
makes a wish to fulfill his heart’s greatest desire.
Dylan Jacobs, played by Ezra Dewey.
Michael Jacobs, played by Rob Brownstein.
Michelle Jacobs, played by Tevy Poe.
The Djinn, played by John Erickson.
The Old Man, played by Donald Pitts.
Mover, played by Jilbert Daniel.
Djinn is a 2013 Emirati supernatural horror film directed
by Tobe Hooper and written by David Tully.
It is set in the United Arab Emirates and features the djinn.
The film, produced by Image Nation, is in both Arabic and English languages.
The film's theatrical release has been delayed since 2011.
Djinn premiered at the Abu Dhabi Film Festival on 25 October 2013.
The film was Hooper's final directorial effort before his death in 2017.
The tone is dark and intense.